

Personal Info

- Lueje Elvis Alonso Lueje
- 34665961749
- @_{elvis.al.95@gmail.com}
- Spanish
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/elvisa
- https://elonso95.github.io/

Skills

Java		
HTML5		
Javascript		
SQL		
Postman		
JUNIT		
GIT		
C#		
Typescript		
HQL		
Firebase		
XML		
Swagger		
SOAPUI		
JAZZ SCM		
Plastic SCM		
Apache		
Subversion		
Mockito		
Jenkins		
Amazon Web		
Services (AWS) Sonarqube		
Microsoft Azure		
Python		
CSS3		
- C33 3		

Languages

Spanish



I am a software developer with 6+ years of experience, specializing in Java, Spring, Vue, and Angular.

I started my journey in Web Application Development, where I participated in an Erasmus+ project, developing a gamified learning web application.

I have worked with various companies, developing robust web applications using Spring Framework and integrating various services and APIs.

I am committed to continuous learning and growth, and I enjoy working in teams and sharing ideas.

Experience

07/2023 - Presente

Software Developer

hiberus - Remote

- Developing microservices apis based on spring boot
- Using tools like postman, sonar, fortify and redhat to ensure the quality and security of my services.

04/2021 - 07/2023

Software Developer

Entornos De Formacion (EDF) - Valencia, Valencian Community Working in educative management systems such as Moodle and

Canvas.

Using technologies from these tools to créate plugins or tools. Being

technologies Java, PHP, JS plus CSS and HTML for the frontend.

11/2020 - 04/2021

Junior Consultant

Capgemini - Valencia, Valencian Community

- Using Spring for microservices with Swagger as the framework for documentation and API testing
- Microservices using SpringBoot
- Using frameworks such as JPA or Hibernate for database access
- Using Angular 10 as front development technology.

07/2017 - 11/2020

Junior Consultant

Capgemini - Langreo, Asturias

- Working with Java web apps with the Apache Struts framework
- Using Spring for microservices with Swagger as the framework for documentation and API testing
- Microservices using SpringBoot
- Using frameworks such as JPA or Hibernate for database access

04/2017 - 06/2017

Developer

Capgemini - Langreo, Asturias

- Working as an ASP.NET developer during practice time from my "Cross platform Application Development" degree.
- Getting files and databases access with the ASP.NET framework.

Education

09/2015 - 06/2017

University of Applied Sciences in Cross Platform Application Development

IES Juan Jose Calvo Miguel - San Martin de Rey Aurelio Promedio: 8.3

- Using differents ways to save data and also accessing that data.
- Using relational databases and their query language (SQL).
- Interface development with Java swing and C#.
- Managing enterprise resources plannings.
- Android apps development.
- Creating webpages with HTML, with CSS.
- Using XML and validating them with DTD or XSD.
- Using linux sistems.
- High level for java development.



>> Software Frameworks

Java

- Apache Struts
- Android
- Srping (MVC, Batch, Boot, Cache)
- JPA
- IDEs: NetBeans, Eclipse

Javascript

- Jquery
- Angular
- Ajax
- ExtJs
- VueJs
- Text Editors: Visual Studio Code, Sublime Text 3

C#

- ASP.NET
- IDEs: Visual Studio

Typescript

- Angular
- Vue

>>> Projects

The Learning Games

- Eramus+

Our project proposes to develop a gamification system of educational delivery that taps into elements from the modern students real world experience and incorporate them into an integral framework that can be used to assess all kinds of learning (formal, primarily, but also informal and non-formal) within the classroom through the achievements the students make in their modules; a system that provides immediate and accessible feedback about performance and the level of mastery acquired and what needs to be learnt in order to progress; a system that improves teacher-student communication, and also student-student communication, a social dimension of learning, which is known to encourage deeper engagement with the activities.

The overall objective is committing the students to change their attitude towards learning, increasing their motivation and consequently enabling them to achieve their full potential.

- Interface with HTML5 & CSS and AngularJS for the behavior of the app.
- Database: Firebase
- HTML Framework: Ionic Framework